<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!-- Generated by LavishSettings v1 -->
<InnerSpaceSettings>
	<Set Name="Chuckisms">
		<setting name="1">Chuck Norris' tears cure cancer. Too bad he has never cried. Ever.</setting>
		<setting name="2">Chuck Norris does not sleep. He waits.</setting>
		<setting name="3">Chuck Norris is currently suing NBC, claiming Law and Order are trademarked names for his left and right legs.</setting>
		<setting name="4">The chief export of Chuck Norris is pain.</setting>
		<setting name="5">If you can see Chuck Norris, he can see you. If you can't see Chuck Norris, you may be only seconds away from death.</setting>
		<setting name="6">Chuck Norris has counted to infinity. Twice.</setting>
		<setting name="7">Chuck Norris does not hunt because the word hunting implies the probability of failure. Chuck Norris goes killing.</setting>
		<setting name="8">Chuck Norris doesn’t wash his clothes, he disembowels them.</setting>
		<setting name="9">Chuck Norris is 1/8th Cherokee. This has nothing to do with ancestry, the man ate a f***ing Indian.</setting>
		<setting name="10">In fine print on the last page of the Guinness Book of World Records it notes that all world records are held by Chuck Norris, and those listed in the book are simply the closest anyone else has ever gotten.</setting>
		<setting name="11">There is no chin behind Chuck Norris' beard. There is only another fist.</setting>
		<setting name="12">Chuck Norris once roundhouse kicked someone so hard that his foot broke the speed of light, went back in time, and killed Amelia Earhart while she was flying over thePacific Ocean.</setting>
		<setting name="13">Crop circles are Chuck Norris' way of telling the world that sometimes corn needs to lie the f*** down.</setting>
		<setting name="14">Chuck Norris is ten feet tall, weighs two-tons, breathes fire, and could eat a hammer and take a shotgun blast standing.</setting>
		<setting name="15">The Great Wall of China was originally created to keep Chuck Norris out. It failed miserably.</setting>
		<setting name="16">If you ask Chuck Norris what time it is, he always says, "Two seconds 'till." After you ask, "Two seconds 'til what?" he roundhouse kicks you in the face.</setting>
		<setting name="17">Chuck Norris drives an ice cream truck covered in human skulls.</setting>
		<setting name="18">Chuck Norris sold his soul to the devil for his rugged good looks and unparalleled martial arts ability. Shortly after the transaction was finalized, Chuck roundhouse-kicked the devil in the face and took his soul back. The devil, who appreciates irony, couldn't stay mad and admitted he should have seen it coming. They now play poker every second Wednesday of the month.</setting>
		<setting name="19">There is no theory of evolution, just a list of creatures Chuck Norris allows to live.</setting>
		<setting name="20">Chuck Norris once ate three 72 oz. steaks in one hour. He spent the first 45 minutes having sex with his waitress.</setting>
		<setting name="21">Chuck Norris is the only man to ever defeat a brick wall in a game of tennis.</setting>
		<setting name="22">Chuck Norris doesn't churn butter. He roundhouse kicks the cows and the butter comes straight out.</setting>
		<setting name="23">When Chuck Norris sends in his taxes, he sends blank forms and includes only a picture of himself, crouched and ready to attack. Chuck Norris has not had to pay taxes ever.</setting>
		<setting name="24">The quickest way to a man's heart is with Chuck Norris' fist.</setting>
		<setting name="25">A Handicap parking sign does not signify that this spot is for handicapped people. It is actually in fact a warning, that the spot belongs to Chuck Norris and that you will be handicapped if you park there.</setting>
		<setting name="26">Chuck Norris will attain statehood in 2009. His state flower will be the Magnolia.</setting>
		<setting name="27">Nagasaki never had a bomb dropped on it. Chuck Norris jumped out of a plane and punched the ground.</setting>
		<setting name="28">Chuck Norris originally appeared in the "Street Fighter II" video game, but was removed by Beta Testers because every button caused him to do a roundhouse kick. When asked bout this "glitch," Norris replied, "That's no glitch."</setting>
		<setting name="29">The opening scene of the movie "Saving Private Ryan" is loosely based on games of dodge ball Chuck Norris played in second grade.</setting>
		<setting name="30">Chuck Norris once shot down a German fighter plane with his finger, by yelling, "Bang!"</setting>
		<setting name="31">Chuck Norris once bet NASA he could survive re-entry without a spacesuit. On July 19th, 1999, a naked Chuck Norris re-entered the earth's atmosphere, streaking over 14 states and reaching a temperature of 3000 degrees. An embarrassed NASA publicly claimed it was a meteor, and still owes him a beer.</setting>
		<setting name="31">Chuck Norris has two speeds: Walk and Kill.</setting>
		<setting name="32">Someone once tried to tell Chuck Norris that roundhouse kicks aren't the best way to kick someone. This has been recorded by historians as the worst mistake anyone has ever made.</setting>
		<setting name="33">Contrary to popular belief, America is not a democracy, it is a Chucktatorship.</setting>
		<setting name="34">Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles is based on a true story: Chuck Norris once swallowed a turtle whole, and when he crapped it out, the turtle was six feet tall and had learned karate.</setting>
		<setting name="35">Chuck Norris is not hung like a horse... horses are hung like Chuck Norris</setting>
		<setting name="36">Chuck Norris is the only human being to display the Heisenberg uncertainty principle -- you can never know both exactly where and how quickly he will roundhouse-kick you in the face.</setting>
		<setting name="37">Chuck Norris can drink an entire gallon of milk in forty-seven seconds.</setting>
		<setting name="38">Rather than being birthed like a normal child, Chuck Norris instead decided to punch his way out of his mother’s womb.</setting>
		<setting name="39">If you say Chuck Norris' name in Mongolia, the people there will roundhouse kick you in his honor. Their kick will be followed by the REAL roundhouse delivered by none other than Norris himself.</setting>
		<setting name="40">Time waits for no man. Unless that man is Chuck Norris.</setting>
		<setting name="41">Chuck Norris discovered a new theory of relativity involving multiple universes in which Chuck Norris is even more badass than in this one. When it was discovered by Albert Einstein and made public, Chuck Norris roundhouse-kicked him in the face. We know Albert Einstein today as Stephen Hawking.</setting>
		<setting name="42">The Chuck Norris military unit was not used in the game Civilization 4, because a single Chuck Norris could defeat the entire combined nations of the world in one turn.</setting>
		<setting name="43">In an average living room there are 1,242 objects Chuck Norris could use to kill you, including the room itself.</setting>
		<setting name="44">Chuck Norris does not teabag the ladies. He potato-sacks them.</setting>
		<setting name="45">Pluto is actually an orbiting group of British soldiers from the American Revolution who entered space after the Chuck gave them a roundhouse kick to the face.</setting>
		<setting name="46">When Chuck Norris goes to donate blood, he declines the syringe, and instead requests a hand gun and a bucket.</setting>
		<setting name="47">There are no weapons of mass destruction. Just Chuck Norris.</setting>
		<setting name="48">Chuck Norris once challenged Lance Armstrong in a "Who has more testicles?" contest. Chuck Norris won by 5.</setting>
		<setting name="49">Chuck Norris was the fourth wise man, who gave baby Jesus the gift of beard, which he carried with him until he died. The other three wise men were enraged by the preference that Jesus showed to Chuck's gift, and arranged to have him written out of the bible. All three died soon after of mysterious roundhouse-kick related injuries.</setting>
		<setting name="50">Chuck Norris sheds his skin twice a year.</setting>
		<setting name="51">When Chuck Norris calls 1-900 numbers, he doesn’t get charged. He holds up the phone and money falls out.</setting>
		<setting name="52">Chuck Norris once ate a whole cake before his friends could tell him there was a stripper in it.</setting>
		<setting name="53">There are no races, only countries of people Chuck Norris has beaten to different shades of black and blue.</setting>
		<setting name="54">Chuck Norris can't finish a "color by numbers" because his markers are filled with the blood of his victims. Unfortunately, all blood is dark red.</setting>
		<setting name="55">A Chuck Norris-delivered Roundhouse Kick is the preferred method of execution in 16 states.</setting>
		<setting name="56">When Chuck Norris falls in water, Chuck Norris doesn't get wet. Water gets Chuck Norris.</setting>
		<setting name="57">Chuck Norris's urine was the main ingredient for balco's designer steroids. Therefore, Chuck Norris is actually the all-time single-season home run king.
</setting>
		<setting name="58">Scientists have estimated that the energy given off during the Big Bang is roughly equal to 1CNRhK (Chuck Norris Roundhouse Kick)</setting>
		<setting name="59">Chuck Norris’ house has no doors, only walls that he walks through.</setting>
		<setting name="60">When Chuck Norris has sex with a man, it won't be because he is gay. It will be because he has run out of women.</setting>
		<setting name="61">How much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could Chuck Norris? ...All of it.</setting>
		<setting name="62">Chuck Norris doesn't actually write books, the words assemble themselves out of fear.</setting>
		<setting name="63">In honor of Chuck Norris, all McDonald's in Texas have an even larger size than the super-size. When ordering, just ask to be "Norrisized".</setting>
		<setting name="64">Chuck Norris CAN believe it's not butter.
</setting>
		<setting name="65">If tapped, a Chuck Norris roundhouse kick could power the country of Australia for 44 minutes.
</setting>
		<setting name="66">The grass is always greener on the other side, unless Chuck Norris has been there. In that case the grass is most likely soaked in blood and tears.
</setting>
		<setting name="67">Newton's Third Law is wrong: Although it states that for each action, there is an equal and opposite reaction, there is no force equal in reaction to a Chuck Norris roundhouse kick.
</setting>
		<setting name="68">Chuck Norris invented his own type of karate. It's called Chuck-Will-Kill.</setting>
		<setting name="69">When an episode of Walker Texas Ranger was aired in France, the French surrendered to Chuck Norris just to be on the safe side.</setting>
		<setting name="70">While urinating, Chuck Norris is easily capable of welding titanium.</setting>
		<setting name="71">Chuck Norris once sued the Houghton-Mifflin textbook company when it became apparent that their account of the war of 1812 was plagiarized from his autobiography.</setting>
		<setting name="72">When Steven Seagal kills a ninja, he only takes its hide. When Chuck Norris kills a ninja, he uses every part.</setting>
		<setting name="73">Wilt Chamberlain claims to have slept with more than 20,000 women in his lifetime. Chuck Norris calls this 'a slow Tuesday.'</setting>
		<setting name="74">Contrary to popular belief, there is indeed enough Chuck Norris to go around.</setting>
		<setting name="75">Chuck Norris doesn’t shave; he kicks himself in the face. The only thing that can cut Chuck Norris is Chuck Norris.</setting>
		<setting name="76">For some, the left testicle is larger than the right one. For Chuck Norris, each testicle is larger than the other one.</setting>
		<setting name="77">When taking the SAT, write "Chuck Norris" for every answer. You will score a 1600.</setting>
		<setting name="78">Chuck Norris invented black. In fact, he invented the entire spectrum of visible light. Except pink. Tom Cruise invented pink.</setting>
		<setting name="79">When you're Chuck Norris, anything + anything is equal to 1. One roundhouse kick to the face.</setting>
		<setting name="80">Chuck Norris has the greatest Poker-Face of all time. He won the 1983 World Series of Poker, despite holding only a Joker, a Get out of Jail Free Monopoly card, a 2 of clubs, 7 of spades and a green #4 card from the game UNO.</setting>
		<setting name="81">On his birthday, Chuck Norris randomly selects one lucky child to be thrown into the sun.</setting>
		<setting name="82">Nobody doesn't like Sara Lee. Except Chuck Norris.</setting>
		<setting name="83">Chuck Norris doesn't throw up if he drinks too much. Chuck Norris throws down!</setting>
		<setting name="84">In the beginning there was nothing...then Chuck Norris Roundhouse kicked that nothing in the face and said "Get a job". That is the story of the universe.</setting>
		<setting name="85">Chuck Norris has 12 moons. One of those moons is the Earth.</setting>
		<setting name="86">Chuck Norris grinds his coffee with his teeth and boils the water with his own rage.</setting>
		<setting name="87">Archeologists unearthed an old English dictionary dating back to the year 1236. It defined "victim" as "one who has encountered Chuck Norris"</setting>
		<setting name="88">Chuck Norris ordered a Big Mac at Burger King, and got one.</setting>
		<setting name="89">Chuck Norris and Mr. T walked into a bar. The bar was instantly destroyed, as that level of awesome cannot be contained in one building.</setting>
		<setting name="90">If you Google search "Chuck Norris getting his ass kicked" you will generate zero results. It just doesn't happen.</setting>
		<setting name="91">Chuck Norris doesn't bowl strikes, he just knocks down one pin and the other nine faint.</setting>
		<setting name="92">The show Survivor had the original premise of putting people on an island with Chuck Norris. there were no survivors and the pilot episode tape has been burned.</setting>
		<setting name="93">Chuck Norris brings the noise AND the funk.</setting>
		<setting name="94">You know how they say if you die in your dream then you will die in real life? In actuality, if you dream of death then Chuck Norris will find you and kill you.</setting>
		<setting name="95">Chuck Norris can slam a revolving door.</setting>
		<setting name="96">When Chuck Norris is in a crowded area, he doesn't walk around people. He walks through them</setting>
		<setting name="97">James Cameron wanted Chuck Norris to play the Terminator. However, upon reflection, he realized that would have turned his movie into a documentary, so he went with Arnold Schwarzenegger.</setting>
		<setting name="98">Chuck Norris can touch MC Hammer.</setting>
		<setting name="99">Little known medical fact: Chuck Norris invented the Caesarean section when he roundhouse-kicked his way out of his mother’s womb.</setting>
		<setting name="100">Chuck Norris can divide by zero.</setting>
	</Set>
	<Set Name="Insults">
		<setting name="1">you are swine.</setting>
		<setting name="2">you are a vulgar little maggot.</setting>
		<setting name="3">you are a worthless bag of filth.</setting>
		<setting name="4">as we say in Texas, you couldn't pour water out of a boot with instructions printed on the heel.</setting>
		<setting name="5">you are a canker, an open wound.</setting>
		<setting name="6">you're a putrescent mass, a walking vomit.</setting>
		<setting name="7">uou are a spineless little worm deserving nothing but the profoundest contempt.</setting>
		<setting name="8">uou are a jerk, a cad, and a weasel.</setting>
		<setting name="9">you are a festering pustule on a weasel's rump.</setting>
		<setting name="10">your life is a monument to stupidity.</setting>
		<setting name="11">you are a stench, a revulsion, a big suck on a sour lemon.</setting>
		<setting name="12">I will never get over the embarrassment of belonging to the same species as you.</setting>
		<setting name="13">you are a monster, an ogre, a malformity.</setting>
		<setting name="14">I barf at the very thought of you..</setting>
		<setting name="15">You have all the appeal of a paper cut.</setting>
		<setting name="16">Lepers avoid you.</setting>
		<setting name="17">you are vile, worthless, less than nothing.</setting>
		<setting name="18">you are a weed, a fungus, the dregs of this earth.</setting>
		<setting name="19">you are a technicolor yawn.</setting>
		<setting name="20">did I mention that you smell?</setting>
		<setting name="21">you are a squeaking rat, a mistake of nature and a heavy-metal bagpipe player.</setting>
		<setting name="22">you were not born. You were hatched into an unwilling world that rejects the likes of you.</setting>
		<setting name="23">your alleged parents abandoned you at birth and then died of shame in recognition of what they had done to an unsuspecting world.</setting>
		<setting name="24">if cluelessness were crude oil, your scalp would be crawling with caribou.</setting>
		<setting name="25">you are a thick-headed trog.</setting>
		<setting name="26">I have seen skeet with more sense than you have.</setting>
		<setting name="27">you are a few bricks short of a full load, a few cards short of a full deck, a few bytes short of a full core dump, and a few chromosomes short of a full human.</setting>
		<setting name="28">God created houseflies, cockroaches, maggots, mosquitos, fleas, ticks, slugs, leeches, and intestinal parasites, then he lowered his standards and made you.</setting>
		<setting name="29">you are the entropy which will claim us all.</setting>
		<setting name="30">you are a green-nostriled, crossed eyed, hairy-livered inbred trout-defiler.</setting>
		<setting name="31">you make Ebola look good.</setting>
		<setting name="32">you are weary, stale, flat and unprofitable.</setting>
		<setting name="33">you are grimy, squalid, nasty and profane.</setting>
		<setting name="34">you are foul and disgusting.</setting>
		<setting name="35">you're a fool, an ignoramus.</setting>
		<setting name="36">monkeys look down on you.</setting>
		<setting name="37">even sheep won't have sex with you.</setting>
		<setting name="38">you are unreservedly pathetic, starved for attention, and lost in a land that reality forgot.</setting>
		<setting name="39">you are not ANSI compliant and your markup doesn't validate.</setting>
		<setting name="40">do you really expect your delusional and incoherent ramblings to be read? </setting>
		<setting name="41">do you fantasize that your tantrums and conniption fits could possibly be worth the pittance of electricity used to send them?</setting>
		<setting name="42">you are a waste of flesh.</setting>
		<setting name="43">you have no rhythm. You are ridiculous and obnoxious.</setting>
		<setting name="44">you are the moral equivalent of a leech.</setting>
		<setting name="45">you are a living emptiness, a meaningless void.</setting>
		<setting name="46">you are sour and senile.</setting>
		<setting name="47">you are a loathsome disease, a drooling inbred cross-eyed toesucker.</setting>
		<setting name="48">you make Quakers shout, and strike Pentecostals silent.</setting>
		<setting name="49">you have a version 1.0 mind in a version 6.1.2 world.</setting>
		<setting name="50">your mother had to tie a pork chop around your neck just to get your dog to play with you.</setting>
		<setting name="51">Hee-Haw is too deep for you.</setting>
		<setting name="52">On a good day you're a half-wit.</setting>
		<setting name="53">You remind me of drool.</setting>
		<setting name="54">you are deficient in all that lends character.</setting>
		<setting name="55">you have the personality of wallpaper.</setting>
		<setting name="56">You are dank and filthy. You are asinine and benighted.</setting>
		<setting name="57">Spammers look down on you.</setting>
		<setting name="58">Phone sex operators hang up on you.</setting>
		<setting name="59">Telemarketers refuse to be seen in public with you.</setting>
		<setting name="60">you spread misery and sorrow wherever you go.</setting>
		<setting name="61">may you choke on your own foolish opinions.</setting>
		<setting name="62">you are a Pusillanimous galactophage and you wear your sister's training bra.</setting>
		<setting name="63">Don't bother opening the door when you leave - you should be able to slime your way out underneath.</setting>
		<setting name="64">I hope that when you get home your mother runs out from under the porch and bites you.</setting>
		<setting name="65">you smarmy lagerlout git. You bloody woofter sod. Bugger off, pillock.</setting>
		<setting name="66">you are a clouted boggish foot-licking half-twit.</setting>
		<setting name="67">your a gob-kissing gleeking flap-mouthed coxcomb.</setting>
		<setting name="68">May your spouse be blessed with many bastards.</setting>
		<setting name="69">you are so clueless that if you dressed in a clue skin, doused yourself in clue musk, and did the clue dance in the middle of a field of horny clues at the height of clue mating season, you still would not have a clue.</setting>
		<setting name="70">if you were a movie you would be a double feature; Battlefield Earth and Ishtar. You would also be out of focus. </setting>
		<setting name="71">you are a fiend and a sniveling coward, and you have bad breath.</setting>
		<setting name="72">you are the unholy spawn of a bandy-legged hobo and a syphilitic camel.</setting>
		<setting name="73">you wear strangely mismatched clothing with oddly placed stains.</setting>
		<setting name="74">you are degenerate, noxious and depraved.</setting>
		<setting name="75">I feel debased just knowing that you exist.</setting>
		<setting name="76">I despise everything about you, and I wish you would go away.</setting>
		<setting name="77">you are jetsam who dreams of becoming flotsam.</setting>
		<setting name="78">I beg for sweet death to come and remove me from a world which became unbearable when you crawled out of a harpy's legs.</setting>
		<setting name="79">it is hard to believe how incredibly dumb you are. Stupid as a stone that the other stones make fun of.</setting>
		<setting name="80">the only thing worse than your logic is your manners.</setting>
	</Set>
</InnerSpaceSettings>